If you want to save this cat,
then bring me a human.
One life is worth as little as any other.
And this is only a cat.
So why do I run?
Why do I search for a human?
Is it to save Meowy?
Such a foolish reason.
I love blood.
The taste, the smell,
the sense of mortality...
And then... there is something
I only recently realized:
The blood is warm...
And feels pleasant.
Why did you save me?
I attempted to kill you.
Such a foolish reason.
Forgive my deceit.
Since Meowy is safe...
You may fondle my chest.
Hell yeah!
Holy shit! Ow!
That hurts!
Can you move?
Not even a finger.
Take Meowy and flee, please.
Damn it, not enough chainsaw...
I must be low on blood.
And after I finally found him...
It's you, right? The one who killed Batty.
He was my man, y'know?!
Oh... but you're actually
pretty cute yourself.
You're my type, so I'll let you go!
What about them?
They die.
Then you can die, too.
He can fight so fiercely...
To merely fondle a chest?
Is this a joke?
How'd a little pupper
like you kill my Batty?
Y'know, he and I shared a dream:
killing and eating all of humanity.
A pipe dream, but a noble one,
and a romantic one.
And now this little
yipping dog has ruined it.
You're cute enough that I regret it...
But you still need to die.
I'm not dying before I cop a feel.
That is ridiculous!
To think he was killed by someone
with such a trashy dream.
Alas, poor Batty...
Such a foolish reason.
Everyone is serious about this except you.
Everybody wants to trash-talk my plans...
It's revenge this,
protect my family that,
and save a cat, too!
Blah, blah, blah!
I guess your fancy dreams
make you guys hot shit, huh?!
How about we have us a dream battle, then?!
How about that?!
If I murderize you,
that means your dream's
weaker than fondling a tit!
Even your howls are cute!
But y'know what they say about
little dogs barking! Yap, yap, yap!
Okay! I'll gobble you up, then!
Go ahead...
If you can beat me in the dream battle!
Demoniacal...
Time to eat...
Kon.
Huh... Huh?
Looks like she's the Leech Devil.
May I swallow?
Do it.
The Leech Devil's extermination is confirmed.
I want the rookies handling search
and rescue, plus assisting with the evac.
Yes, sir!
Okay!
Himeno, you've got seniority,
so keep watch for more devils.
On it.
Dream battle... Gonna... My dream battle...
You and the Blood Fiend
need to be debriefed.
And Meowy?
Have the cat sent to a veterinarian
for a thorough checkup.
I found your arm.
A blood infusion was all
it needed to reattach.
You really are like a devil.
You seemed pretty friendly
with that devil back there.
I saw.
You really don't know a thing, huh?
Devil Hunters form contracts with
devils in order to fight against them.
I've got a contract with the Fox Devil.
In exchange for power,
I offer up a bit of my body as food.
It was some skin this time.
Sounds painful.
Devils yearn for the deaths of humans.
The same goes for Fiends.
Power seems cool, though.
The surveillance cameras caught
you two headed to your patrol area.
Paused
And the house that we believe
was housing the Bat Devil
contained a lot of your spilt blood.
The Blood Fiend tried to kill you, didn't she?
I don't know why, but you're trying
to protect a devil. Again.
I dunno... is that how it happened?
My daughter would like
to meet the chainsaw guy.
Thank you.
The devil threatened to eat
me back at the office,
but now that I think about it, he was
wearing a Public Safety uniform.
I'd like to thank him.
"Don't give a shit about
saving some dude," he says!
And then the devil throws
my car with me in it!
It was a devil with a chainsaw
coming out of its head...
If I dig deeper into this,
and report it to the higher-ups,
it'd mean the Blood Fiend gets disposed of
along with you, since you covered for her.
But there were no fatalities.
So, if you're willing to accept one condition,
I'll let what happened slide.
You need to do what I tell you to.
You're a dumbass and a brat
with no clue about right and wrong.
I've been doing this longer, so I'm pretty
sure I have some grasp of social ethics.
All you need to do to protect
this lifestyle is listen to me.
How about it? If you follow,
I want an answer.
Sure. I'll keep it in mind.
You can relax.
I might not be after some
big-deal goal like you guys,
and I might dream small.
But I'm as serious about this as you are.
You can count on me.
Try and learn some manners in the meantime.
Yeah, I'll think about it.
You see? Am I not innocent?
Now, would you kindly take these off?
Is this a good idea?
When this cutie-Fiend kills somebody,
it's gonna be your responsibility,
for letting her live.
We're Devil Hunters.
Whether they're devils or Fiends,
if they're handy,
we should put them to work.
But they're still the enemy.
We're just making use of them.
We're not making friends.
Come in.
Excuse me.
And he claims they "were outside
the patrol zone before they knew it,"
and that they discovered a house that
"looked like it had a super-nasty devil in it,"
which is where they encountered
the Bat Devil.
Denji used his chainsaws to
exterminate the Bat Devil,
and then came under attack
by the Leech Devil...
Which Division 4 exterminated.
There were no traces of Gun flesh
in either the Bat or Leech Devil's heads.
That concludes my report.
Well done.
But Denji and Power managed to get awfully
far without anyone noticing, didn't they?
I'd chalk that up to them
being unbelievably stupid.
Leaving the approved area
is against regulations.
Considering there were no fatalities,
and that we were able to get rid of
two devils, I think it's worth overlooking.
Understood.
If you'll excuse me, ma'am.
You seem a little more
flexible now, Hayakawa.
Is that Denji's influence, I wonder?
I doubt it.
I haven't changed at all.
How's he up so early?
What's for lunch?
Curry.
Sweet!
The hell's this? A devil?
What a pitiful home this is!
I'd like you to put Power up
in one of your rooms, Hayakawa.
I think you'll make a good leash
for the two of them.
Stop right there, Meowy!
Is there some reason why you're sending
me all these psychos, ma'am?
It seems you've got quite a feast!
It's because I trust you
more than anyone else.
Damn it, who said you could come in?!
'Tis mine now!
Gimme my super toast back!
Oh... okay.
It'd be a little odd to have her
staying at the office indefinitely.
Okay.
You don't need to worry.
Power said she would behave.
It'll be fine.
Vegetables are revolting!
Away!
Carrot!
Don't fling your vegetables!
Damn it...
Show some respect to the farmers
who grew the veggies, devil!
The toilet?
I prefer to only occasionally
flush my feces.
Flush it!
It stinks.
I prefer to only occasionally bathe.
Get in there!
You reek!
You two are absurd.
How delicate these humans be.
Aren't they, Meowy?
Can't believe she just shows up
and starts raising hell.
Do devils not flush the toilet?
Didn't eat her veggies either.
You there...
Hey, Shit Devil! Your turds are stuck
to the damn toilet and won't come off!
We had a deal, did we not?
You may fondle my chest.
So, fondle!
Come now, what's the matter?
Aren't you pleased?
Commence your fondling.
I have stipulations, however.
You have earned three squeezes of my breast.
Three?
One for your rescue of Meowy.
A second for slaying the Bat Devil.
And a third for protecting me from topknot!
I had no intention of actually letting you,
but your efforts have earned
you these three squeezes.
Squeeze them gratefully.
She's an angel!
BLAAAARGH!
Lalalalah
Denji,
Hear
Me
Out